stipple.com 2015-10-02

# Stipple's Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Latest Revision: July 25, 2012

Unless otherwise defined in this Policy, terms used in this Policy have the same meanings as in our Stipple User Terms of Service.

We take your privacy seriously. We are providing this Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information through the Service. We also want to inform you about your choices regarding information. If you have any questions or concerns, please let us know (see “How to Contact Us” section below).

As used in this Policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization. Stipple, Inc. is the corporate name for Stipple. In this Policy, we will refer to Stipple Inc. as **“Stipple”** , **“our”** , **“us”** or **“we.”**

Note that this Policy may be modified from time to time in our sole discretion, so please check for updated versions periodically. We will notify you of any changes to this Policy by posting a new Policy and updating the “last modified” date at the bottom of this page.

#### How We Collect Information

First, we collect information that you voluntarily provide to become a registered User of the Service, and when you use certain aspects of the Service.

Second, we collect information when you register to join Stipple by logging into an account that you already have with certain third-party social networking sites (“SNS”) (including, but not limited to, Facebook, Twitter, Flickr, Instagram, Google+ and Etsy) via the Service. For example, the Service allows you to create an account and login to the Service using your Facebook account credentials through Facebook Connect. If you are not currently registered as a User on the Service and sign onto Stipple using Facebook, you will first be asked to enter your Facebook credentials and then be given the option to register and join Stipple.

Third, when you browse or use the Service, technological tools including “Log Data” and “Cookies” collect certain information, as explained in the following section.

**Personal Information.** When you register with us through the Service to become a registered User of Stipple, we will ask you for certain information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“ **Personal Information** ”). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, gender, profile photo, free-form biography, location, website and email address. If you decide to create your User account by logging into a SNS via the Service, you are using the Personal Information you have already provided to the SNS (such as your “real” name, email address and other information you make publicly available via the SNS) to create your User account on the Service; the information we collect may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNS, so please consult the SNS’s privacy and data practices.

We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your “Non-Identifying Information” defined below) to provide the Service to you. For example:

1) We create your User account for your use of the Service based upon the Personal Information you provide.

2) We use your Personal Information to contact you with Stipple newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or update your “preferences” information in your account settings. (See “Your Choices Regarding Information,” below.)

3) We use your Personal Information to respond to your questions and/or inquiries.

4) You also may have the option to import your personal contacts (including email addresses of friend lists via SNS) to the Service so that you can find your friends on the Service, and your friends can find you on the Service.

5) As part of the Service, Stipple Users may communicate with other registered and non-registered Users through use of their Stipple accounts.

_Non-Identifying Information._ We also collect other information that you provide as part of registration, the operation, and personalization of your account with Stipple that cannot reasonably be used to identify or contact you (e.g., without limitation, age and individual preferences) (“ **Non-Identifying Information** ”). Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be personally identified or contacted. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other Non-Identifying Information (for example, your viewing preferences). We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Stipple Users to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how the Service is used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.

_Log Data._ When you use the Service, whether as a registered User or a non-registered User just browsing, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“ **Log Data** ”). This Log Data may include information such as the browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to Stipple’s website, pages of the Service that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on the Service, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Service and the Service’s technical administration, to increase the Service’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor the Service to our visitors’ needs. For example, some of this information is collected so that when you use the Service again, it will recognize you and the information could then be used to serve advertisements and other information appropriate to your interests. We also use this information to verify that users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests.

_Cookies._ Like many online services, Stipple uses “cookies” with the Service to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer or mobile device’s hard disk. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize “persistent” cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Service. Second, we utilize “session ID” cookies to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage by Stipple Users and web traffic routing through the Service. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Service and then close your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Service or all functionality of the Service. (See “Your Choices Regarding Information,” below.)

#### Sharing of Your Information

When you register through the Service and submit Personal Information to create a profile or visual collection, other Stipple Users will see your name and profile. If you choose to provide additional Personal Information in your profile, Stipple Users will see such additional Personal Information, including, but not limited to, your photo, location, website and biography. Providing additional Personal Information is voluntary and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with other Stipple Users. We recommend that you guard and refrain from disclosing any information you consider sensitive and confidential.

_Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information._ We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

_Service Providers._ We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services (e.g., maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Service’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how the Service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

_Social Networking Sites._ We may share the information in your Stipple account (including your Personal Information) with the SNSs that you have linked to your Stipple account. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only for this purpose (unless the SNS has received your Personal Information independently of the Service) and not for other purposes.

#### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Stipple cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We can disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process including, but not limited to, subpoenas, to protect the property and rights of Stipple or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

#### Business Transfers

Stipple may sell, divest, transfer, assign, share or otherwise engage in a transaction that involves, some or all of our assets, including any or all of the information described in this Policy, in the course of a corporate divestiture, merger, acquisition, joint venture, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or any other similar transaction or proceeding.

#### Your Choices Regarding Information

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive email notifications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or update your “preferences” information in your account settings.

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to accept cookies through the Service for any of the purposes described above, then you can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Consult your browser’s technical information. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Service or all functionality of the Service.

As discussed above, we allow Users to link their Facebook, Twitter, Google, Flickr, Instagram, Google+ and Etsy accounts through the Service. Users can then post recent activity on the Service back to their SNS accounts. You can disable the foregoing feature at any time by logging into your account settings and selecting the option to disable one or more SNSs. Further, you may be able to edit your privacy settings for the content that you post which appears on a SNS by making selections in your account settings via the Service.

All Users may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their User account. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

#### Links to Other Sites and Services

The Service contains links to other third-party websites and online services. If you choose to visit another website or online service by clicking on a link, you will be directed to that third party’s website or online service. The fact that we may link to a website or online service is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites and online services, and these third parties may place their own cookies or other files on your computer and collect data or solicit Personal Information and Non-Identifying Information from you. Other sites and online services follow different rules regarding the collection, use and/or disclosure of Personal Information and Non-Identifying Information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites or online services you visit before providing any information or using such websites or services.

#### How We Store and Protect Information

We care about the security of your information. We use commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of information collected and maintained through the Service. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by unauthorized persons.

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to Stipple. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not request your credit card information, login information, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Service in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Stipple transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

#### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Policy or any of the practices described herein, please send us an email at [support@stipple.com](mailto:support@stipple.com).
